{
    "text": "I understand much better why America's political elites behave the way they behave now that I know about what kind… https://t.co/9epkhHasA8",
    "url": "https://twitter.com/anyuser/status/1044465230317645824",
    "images": [
        "https://pbs.twimg.com/profile_images/831025272589676544/3g6BrXCE_normal.jpg"
    ],
    "retweets": 15,
    "favourites": 139,
    "sentiment": {
        "magnitude": 0.10000000149011612,
        "score": 0.10000000149011612
    },
    "entities": [
        {
            "elites": {
                "entity salience": 0.6416717767715454,
                "entity type": "PERSON"
            }
        },
        {
            "way": {
                "entity salience": 0.1649588644504547,
                "entity type": "OTHER"
            }
        },
        {
            "America": {
                "entity salience": 0.14399687945842743,
                "entity type": "LOCATION"
            }
        },
        {
            "https://t.co/9epkhHasA8": {
                "entity salience": 0.04937249422073364,
                "entity type": "OTHER"
            }
        }
    ],
    "children": [
        {
            "text": "@fchollet America's plutocracy isn't too new, but yeah, the political elite have always run in the same circles, ou… https://t.co/kreo2mPdZD",
            "url": "https://twitter.com/anyuser/status/1044760267379363845",
            "images": [
                "https://pbs.twimg.com/profile_images/771457767672459264/fGku3qGt_normal.jpg"
            ],
            "retweets": 0,
            "favourites": 0,
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.0,
                "score": 0.0
            },
            "entities": [
                {
                    "@fchollet America": {
                        "entity salience": 0.38170504570007324,
                        "entity type": "PERSON"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "plutocracy": {
                        "entity salience": 0.3086126148700714,
                        "entity type": "OTHER"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "elite": {
                        "entity salience": 0.1748134195804596,
                        "entity type": "PERSON"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "circles": {
                        "entity salience": 0.13486889004707336,
                        "entity type": "OTHER"
                    }
                }
            ],
            "children": []
        },
        {
            "text": "@fchollet You’re ok just because nobody is interested in taking you down. Try to play and we’ll see.",
            "url": "https://twitter.com/anyuser/status/1044733311392854016",
            "images": [
                "https://pbs.twimg.com/profile_images/530852429055938560/JccIf-qR_normal.jpeg"
            ],
            "retweets": 0,
            "favourites": 0,
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 1.0,
                "score": -0.20000000298023224
            },
            "entities": [
                {
                    "@fchollet": {
                        "entity salience": 0.6380255222320557,
                        "entity type": "PERSON"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "nobody": {
                        "entity salience": 0.36197444796562195,
                        "entity type": "PERSON"
                    }
                }
            ],
            "children": []
        },
        {
            "text": "@fchollet What explains the behavior of French  elites?",
            "url": "https://twitter.com/anyuser/status/1044697761088753664",
            "images": [
                "https://pbs.twimg.com/profile_images/974803369800867840/XC6uVGRz_normal.jpg"
            ],
            "retweets": 0,
            "favourites": 0,
            "sentiment": {
                "magnitude": 0.10000000149011612,
                "score": 0.10000000149011612
            },
            "entities": [
                {
                    "@fchollet": {
                        "entity salience": 0.5200040936470032,
                        "entity type": "PERSON"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "behavior": {
                        "entity salience": 0.25231125950813293,
                        "entity type": "OTHER"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "elites": {
                        "entity salience": 0.17912742495536804,
                        "entity type": "PERSON"
                    }
                },
                {
                    "French": {
                        "entity salience": 0.04855724051594734,
                        "entity type": "LOCATION"
                    }
                }
            ],
            "children": []
        }
    ]
}